Guide to the Toni Beauchamp Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Other Works, id166259
  - Various Printed Material, Publications, Articles, id166573
    - National Center for Nonprofit Board, 1992-1993; id167091 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - David Theis, 2002; id167092 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Museum and Arts Houston, 1992; id167093 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Imagine Houston, 1994; id167094 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Preservation News, 1994; id167095 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Giving Wisely and General Nonprofit Charity Info, undated; id167096 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Texas Accountants and Lawyers for the Arts, 1995-1998; id167097 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - National Dispatch at MFA,H and CAM,H, 1982-1985; id167098 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Americans for the Arts Figure, 1999; id167099 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Art Lies, 1995-2006; id167100 (Box 35, Folder 36-37)
    - Imagine Houston, 1995; id167101 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Arts Houston, 2006-2007; id167103 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - UH Blaffer Art Museum, 2008; id167104 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Experts, 1978-1989; id167105 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Cultural Issue, 1998-1999; id167106 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Donor Surveys, undated; id167107 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Foundations Ref, 2003; id167108 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Phillip Locate– Small Press, 1984-1986; id167109 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Fundraising Ref, 1997-2004; id167110 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Diet and Supplement Manipulative, 2007; id167111 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Houston Visual Arts, 1984; id167112 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Interviewing, 1986-1992; id167113 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - ANP Collector’s Forum, 1985-1986; id167114 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Conducting Meetings, 1988; id167115 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Subscriptions, 1994-1996; id167116 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Reader File, 1992-1993; id167117 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - American Society of Landscape Architecture, undated; id167118 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Coalition of Nonprofit Organizations, 1980-1983; id167119 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Houston Festival, 1983; id167120 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Rosters, 1987-1988; id167121 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Thank-You Notes and Invitations, undated; id167122 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Portfolio Management, 1983; id167123 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Seven Habits of Highly Effective People, undated; id167124 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Buffalo Bayou Partnership, undated; id167125 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Toni Beauchamp’s Personal Notes, undated; id167126 (Box 36, Folder 24-25)
  - Government Affiliation with Arts, id166574
    - Public Policy, 1998; id167128 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Local Government and the Arts, undated; id167129 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Carlos Jiménez, id166575
    - Clippings, undated; id167132 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Various, undated; id167131 (Box 36, Folder 29-30)
  - Untitled Works, id166576
    - Various Associations’ Information, 1995-2003; id167135 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Financials, 1987-2008; id167136 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Printed Materials, undated; id167137 (Box 37, Folder 3-15)
    - Printed Materials, undated; id167138 (Box 38, Folder 1-9)
  - Textbooks, id166577
    - Financial Management for Arts Organization, undated; id167140 (Box 38, Item 10)
    - Conflict in the Arts: The Relocation of Authority, 1975; id167141 (Box 38, Item 11)
    - Cases in Arts Administration, 1975; id167142 (Box 38, Item 12)
- Newspaper and Magazine Clippings/Full Newspapers, id166260
  This series consists of full newspapers and newspaper and magazine clippings that contain information regarding the various projects with which Toni Beauchamp was affiliated, as well as general subject matters that were of interest to her. Some of the topics that can be found in this series include Robert Wilson, arts and architecture, John Biggers, Market Square Park, and real estate, among others.
  - Newspaper Clippings, id167143
    - Robert Wilson, 1999-2003; id167147 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Arts and Architecture, 1994-2005; id167148 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - DiverseWorks, 1985-2006; id167149 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - The Orange Show, 1980-1997; id167150 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Millennium Project, 1995-2001; id167151 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - The Menil, 1979-2007; id167152 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Real Estate / Business, 1984-2001; id167153 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Downtown, 1983-2002; id167154 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Opera, 1981-1988; id167155 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Shelby Hodge, 1991-2002; id167156 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Individuals Personal Achievements, 1978-2009; id167157 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - John Biggers, 1980-1995; id167158 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Buffalo Bayou, 1982-2006; id167159 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Market Square Park, 1976-1993; id167160 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Houston History, 1982-2004; id167161 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Television and Music, 1992-2006; id167162 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Sarah Blaffer, 1967-2001; id167163 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Politics Relating to Art and General, 1989-2002; id167164 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1957-1999; id167165 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - FotoFest, 1996-1998; id167166 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Jim Barlow, 1991-1998; id167167 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Lawndale, 1987-1992; id167168 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Cultural Art Council Houston, 1980-1996; id167169 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Obituaries, 1989-2010; id167170 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Houston Symphonies, 1983-2011; id167171 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Tom Marshall, 1997-2002; id167172 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Books Reviews and Publishing, 1976-2006; id167174 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - MFA,H, 1980-2005; id167175 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Art Exhibit, 1983-2005; id167176 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Contemporary Art Museums, 1978-2004; id167177 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Rick Lowe Housing, 1994-2006; id167178 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Ballet, 1983-1998; id167179 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Galleries, 1964-2006; id167180 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Business, 1979-2002; id167181 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Nature, 1979-2006; id167182 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Medicine, 1992-2001; id167183 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Sculpture, 1981-2000; id167184 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Museum, 1980-2002; id167185 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Events in the Art World, 1979-2007; id167186 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Events in the Art World, 1979-2007; id167187 (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
    - Sweeney Social and Cultural History, undated; id167188 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981-2006; id167189 (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
  - Full Newspapers, id167144
    - Art, 1982-2007; id167191 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Rothko Chapel, 2001; id167192 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Business, 1982-1993; id167193 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Houston, 1999-2001; id167194 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Houston Symphony, 1980; id167195 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Architecture, 1991; id167196 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Real Estate, 1995-1999; id167197 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Medicine, 1995; id167198 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Robert Wilson, 1992; id167199 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Various, 1993-2006; id167200 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Magazine Clippings, id167145
    - Medicine, 1988-2009; id167202 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Art and Architecture, 1983-1997; id167203 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Art, 1984-2006; id167204 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Fashion, 1982-2007; id167205 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - About Houston, 1980-2006; id167206 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Benefactor, 1990-1997; id167207 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Robert Wilson, 1992-1998; id167208 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Sweeney, 1966-1980; id167209 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Various, 1982-2007; id167210 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Photographs, id166261
  This series consists of photographs of various projects and events in which Toni Beauchamp was engaged. The pictures consist of projects such as; DiverseWorks, Market Square Park, and the Millennium Project, among others. Each project and event is separated into folders as listed below:
  - DiverseWorks, undated; id167212 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Buffalo Bayou Negatives and Discs, 1997; id167213 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Millennium Project, undated; id167214 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - San Antonio River Walk, 2002; id167215 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Obituary, 1994; id167216 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Museum of Fine Art, Houston, 1980; id167217 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - FotoFest, 1990; id167218 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Market Square Park, undated; id167219 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - CACHH, Public Affair Law, 1985-1986; id167220 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Leadership Houston, undated; id167221 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Sweeney, undated; id167222 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Professional Development and Consulting, undated; id167223 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Tiden-Foley Gallery, 1987; id167224 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Various Special Events, undated; id167225 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous, undated; id167226 (Box 40, Folder 40)
- Audiovisual and digital, id166262
  This series consists of VCD’S, CD’s and Disk players that contains information relating to the various projects and events in which Toni Beauchamp was engaged. These projects include; Buffalo Bayou Park, DiverseWorks, Market Square Park, James Johnson Sweeney, Toni’s thesis research, and Friends of Integrative Medicine.
  - DiverseWorks DiverseDialogues, 1997-1998; id167228 (Box 41, Item 1)
  - The Market Square Project the Municipal Channel, 1992; id167229 (Box 41, Item 2)
  - Various Untitled Market Square Park Project Videos, undated; id167230 (Box 41, Item 3)
  - Buffalo Bayou Partnership Master Plan CD, 2001; id167231 (Box 41, Item 4)
  - Buffalo Bayou Partnership Project Map CD, 2001; id167232 (Box 41, Item 5)
  - Buffalo Bayou Partnership NSSTF CD, undated; id167233 (Box 41, Item 6)
  - Malachi Farrell CD, undated; id167234 (Box 41, Item 7)
  - Friends of Integrative Medicine Complementary Therapies CD, 2003; id167235 (Box 41, Item 8)
  - Friends of Integrative Medicine Place of Wellness CD, 2003; id167236 (Box 41, Item 9)
  - Artpace Anniversary CD, undated; id167237 (Box 41, Item 10)
  - Artpace: “because arts matters” CD, undated; id167238 (Box 41, Item 11)
  - Artpace “another day at artpace” CD, undated; id167239 (Box 41, Item 12)
  - Artpix 1-3, 1998, 1999, 2001; id167240 (Box 41, Item 13)
  - Unlabeled CD, undated; id167241 (Box 41, Item 14)
  - 5.25 Floppy Disk Sweeney Bio, undated; id167242 (Box 41, Item 15)
  - 5.25 Floppy Disk Sweeney MFA,H History, undated; id167243 (Box 41, Item 16)
  - 5.25 Floppy Disk Sweeney MFA,H History 2 (backup), undated; id167244 (Box 41, Item 17)
  - 5.25 Floppy Disk Sweeney Thesis Biography, undated; id167245 (Box 41, Item 18)
  - 5.25 Floppy Disk Sweeney MFA,H Exhibits, undated; id167246 (Box 41, Item 19-20)
  - 5.25 Floppy Disk Sweeney Thesis Questions, undated; id167248 (Box 41, Item 21)
  - 5.25 Floppy Disk Sweeney Thesis Bibliography, undated; id167249 (Box 41, Item 22)
  - 5.25 Floppy Disk Sweeney Table of Contents, undated; id167250 (Box 41, Item 23)
  - 5.25 Floppy Disk Sweeney Bibliography Combined, undated; id167251 (Box 41, Item 24)
  - Microcassette, undated; id167252 (Box 41, Item 25)
- Ephemera/Index Cards, id166263
  This series consist of Ephemera such as awards given to Toni Beauchamp and Index cards that she used to take notes while carrying out various research for projects.
  - Ephemera, id167253
    - Private Dinner Preview of Granite Sculpture, 1986; id167257 (Box 42, Item 1)
    - Houston Alumni Organization Century Club, undated; id167258 (Box 42, Item 2)
    - Outstanding Community Volunteer Award, undated; id167259 (Box 42, Item 3)
    - Patrons Recognition Award, 2000; id167260 (Box 42, Item 4)
    - International Sculpture Center, undated; id167261 (Box 42, Item 5)
    - Market Square Park Stamp, undated; id167262 (Box 42, Item 6)
    - Cultural Arts Council Houston Board Arts Directors Name Tag, undated; id167263 (Box 42, Item 7)
    - Toni Beauchamp UT Austin Certificate, id167264 (Ovsbox 1, Item 1)
    - The Deans Circle Award at University of Houston, undated; id167265 (Ovsbox 1, Item 3)
  - Index Cards, id167254
    - Sweeney Research Index Cards, undated; id167269 (Box 43, Item 1)
    - Sweeney Index Cards, MFA,H and Miscellanea, undated; id167270 (Box 44, Item 1)
    - Sweeney Research Index Cards, id167271 (Box 45, Item 1)